منال الجنبى **MANAL ALJANABI**

الهدف الوظيفي CAREER OBJECTIVE

I have over 5 years of customer service experience, Secretarial and Sale, with strong communication skills in different fields and a wide range of experience in computer and marketing.

لدى أكثر من 5 سنوات من الخبرة في خدمة العملاء ، السكرتارية والبيع ، مع مهارات اتصال قوية في مختلف المجالات ومجموعة واسعة من الخبرة في الكمبيوتر والتسويق.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Mathematics King Saud University (Riyadh)
- Diploma of Business & Information Technology AL Hussan Institutes (Dammam)
- Diploma of Cyber security Inspire London College (London)

التعليم

- بكالوربوس رياضيات جامعة الملك سعود (الرياض)
- دبلوم الأعمال وتكنولوجيا المعلومات معاهد الحصان (الدمام)
- دبلوم الأمن السيبراني Inspire London College (لندن)

EXPERIENCES

- Crowd Management King Abdulaziz Center For World Culture (Ithra) - Dhahran (Aug 2018 - Current)
- Secretary Qatif Charity Association Qatif (Aug 2016 -Aug 2018)
- Customer Service Agent & Sales Representative Arab National Bank - Dammam (Sep 2014 - May 2015)
- Call Center Agent Sanabis Communication Technology Training - Qatif (Feb 2010 - Apr 2011)

الخبرات

- إدارة الزوار مركز الملك عبدالعزيز للثقافة العالمية (إثراء) -الظهران (أغسطس 2018 - حتى الآن)
 - سكرتير جمعية القطيف الخيرية القطيف (أغسطس 2016 - أغسطس 2018)
 - وكيلة خدمة العملاء وممثلة المبيعات البنك العربي الوطني - الدمام (سبتمبر 2014 - مايو 2015)
- وكيلة مركز الاتصال تدريب تكنولوجيا الاتصالات سنابس - القطيف (فبراير 2010 - أبريل 2011)

COURSES

- · Cyber security expert in cooperation with the SDAIA & Misk
- Professional project management
- Recent trends in communications by Stc
- Administrative coordination and development of secretarial
- Communication skills
- Human resources management
- Leadership and supervision skills
- Computer Skills
- Commitment \Fight against financial fraud, Money laundering and financing of terrorism by ANB
- · Mandates of Consumer Finance by ANB
- Mahara Program (Training program for IT Graduates intended to develop their English, Soft Skills and IT competencies) Sponsored by PMPYD and WIPRO
- Bank account
- Level 1 BTEC Foundation Award in INTRODUCTION TO CONTACT CENTERS by Edexcel

الدورات

- خبير الأمن السيبراني بالتعاون مع الهيئة السعودية للبيانات والذكاء الاصطناعي و مسك الخيرية
 - إدارة المشاريع الإحترافية
 - الاتجاهات الحديثة في الاتصالات من قبل شركة Stc
 - التنسيق الإداري وتنمية مهارات السكرتارية
 - مهارات التواصل
 - إدارة الموارد البشرية
 - مهارات القيادة والإشراف
 - مهارات الحاسوب
- مكافحة الاحتيال المالي وغسيل الأموال وتمويل الإرهاب من قبل البنك العربي الوطني
 - تفويضات البنك العربى الوطنى لتمويل المستهلك
- برنامج مهارة (برنامج تدريبي لخريجي تكنولوجيا المعلومات يهدف إلى تطوير لغتهم الإنجليزية ومهاراتهم الشخصية وكفاءاتهم في مجال تكنولوجيا المعلومات) برعاية PMPYD و
 - الحساب البنكي
- جائزة مؤسسة BTEC في المستوى 1 مقدمة لمراكز الاتصال من قبل Edexcel







Volunteer

التطوع

• Volunteer as a social researcher for a charity

• تطوع كباحث اجتماعي لجمعية خيرية

المهارات Skills

- Computer proficiency
- · Time management strength
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- Fast learning ability
- Communication skills
- Planning and organization
- I can working both individually and as a team
- member
- Leadership
- English











• العربية

- إجادة إستخدام الحاسب الألي
 - قوة إدارة الوقت
- إدارة علاقات العملاء (CRM)
 - القدرة على التعلم السريع
 - مهارات التواصل
 - التخطيط والتنظيم
- العمل بشكل فردي وكعضو من الفريق
 - القيادة

